Jerald Baroro

Web Developer

Goal-oriented Web Developer brings strong commitment to collaboration and solutions-oriented problem-solving. Use various web design packages to develop custom-crafted, customer-focused websites and designs. Committed to high standards of user experience, usability and speed. Lends detailed knowledge of Node and React Web Development.

Work History

2019-11 -2021-01

Process Executive

Cognizant Philippines, Cebu City, Cebu · Answered telephone or online requests and

- completed interactions quickly to meet productivity goals.
- · Collaborated with team to define business requirements for organizational processes, achieve productivity standards and adhere to accuracy standards

2019-07 -2021-10

Customer Service Representative Teleperformance IT Park, Cebu City, Cebu

Achieved and consistently exceeded revenue

- quota through product and service promotion during routine calls. Offered advice and assistance to customers,
- paving attention to special needs or wants.
- Responded to customer requests for products. services and company information.

Education

2017-06 -2019-04

Associate of Science: Information Technology

Siquijor State College - Lazi Campus - Tigbawan, Lazi, Siguijor

2008-06 -2012-04

High School Diploma

Lazi National Agricultural School - Tiabawan, Lazi, Siquijor

2011-06 -2012-04

Computer Hardware Servicina NC II: Computer Hardware Servicina

Lazi National Agricultural School - Tigbawan, Lazi, Siguijor

Certifications

2020-10 The Complete 2020 Web Development Bootcamp

2020-11 Advanced CSS and Sass: Flexbox, Grid, Animations

and More! 2020-12

Node with React: Fullstack Web Development

Contact

Address Cebu City, CEB, 6000

Phone 09667652125

F-mail

spaueOfficial@gmail.com

@spaueOfficial

www

https://ieralddev.herokuapp.com/

Skills

Sales expertise

Credit card processing

.... Software Best Practices

Programming Languages

....

....

....

....

....

....

....

....

....

IMTH

JavaScript 5 1

Programming

Layout development Analytical skills

C Proficiency

ReactJS

MongoDB

Node IS

Photoshop

Tailwindcss